翻译、时间轴、压制：up主
Hi everyone! We're here to introduce War Thunder update 1.61: Road to glory.
大家好 欢迎来到战争雷霆1.61版本更新：光荣之路
Update 1.61 is small in size, but very exciting in content.
1.61版本更新体积虽然不大 但是内容亦可赛艇
New airplanes and tanks, a new system of squadron battles,
新的空中和地面载具 新的联队战斗系统
improvements to gameplay and in-game models.
增强的游戏体验和新的游戏内模型
War Thunder 1.61 is sure to make all our players happy.
战争雷霆1.61一定会让我们的所有玩家一起哈啤
Let's take a look at the new arrivals in more detail.
让我们仔细看看这次更新的内容
The P-47N-15, the late-series Thunderbolt, a heavy, powerful and awesome aircraft.
P-47N-15 雷电系列的最后一个型号 重量和火力都十足的飞机
One of the most modern piston-engine fighters,
最后的活塞螺旋桨战斗机之一
and possibly the heaviest single-engine fighter in the game.
也可能是游戏里最重的单引擎战斗机
Thanks to its powerful engine, it can reach speeds of over 750 km/h,
得益于其强大的引擎 它能达到的最大速度超过750km/h
worth 466 miles an hour.
差不多466mi/h
It perfectly restores energy after banking maneuvers and it can withstand incredible g-forces.
它在滚转中的存能性能很好 同时还能承受巨大的过载
It has eight high-caliber Brownings, bombs, rockets and "bazookas".
它的武器为八门大口径勃朗宁机枪 炸弹 火箭弹和“巴祖卡”
It's a flying arsenal that rains down destruction on its enemies at breakneck speeds.
就像飞行着的军火库一样 它能以极快的速度对敌人发动枪林弹雨般的攻击
The Ki-100 – an addition to the Japanese army fighter line.
Ki-100 日本战斗机科技树的新载具
Based on the late-series Ki-61, this fighter was equipped with an air-cooled engine.
基于之前的Ki-61系列 这架战斗机装备着一台风冷发动机
The new engine is slightly inferior to its predecessor in terms of speed,
尽管这台新引擎在速度上不如它的前辈
but it's much better in reliability and fire-resistance.
但是在可靠性和耐火性上更胜一筹
The new carrier-borne F7F Tigercat fighter
海航版的F7F虎猫战斗机
will become available to participants of our “Operation Summer” special event.
将会成为“Operation Summer”这场特殊活动参与者的奖品
One of the most dangerous and most popular twin-engine fighters
作为最危险也是最具人气的双引擎战斗机
is now capable of carrying the destructive Tiny Tim anti-ship rockets.
能够装备威力巨大的小蒂姆反舰火箭弹
The fighter also has premium status,
这架战斗机同时也是高级载具
so the new Tigercat will bring its owner lots of fun along with heaps of Silver Lions and research points.
所以这架新虎猫在给其拥有着带来游戏乐趣的同时带来大量银狮和研发点收益
Haven't entered the “Operation Summer” yet?
还没参加“Operation Summer”呢
Hurry up! You can find out the details on our official site.
抓紧 你能在我们官网上找到更多关于此活动的细节
We're continuing to work on replacing old in-game models with new ones.
我们仍不遗余力地推进着更换老模型的工作
A new awesome appearance has been given to the British Spitfire Mk.IV Model F
英国的喷火Mk.IV F型获得了新的帅气的外形
along with one of the first airplanes in the game, the German Heinkel 111 H-6, a true old timer!
同时作为游戏内的第一批空战载具 德国亨克尔111H-6的模型也获得了更换
This rejuvenated old workhorse has also received two machine gun turrets
这架老载具在获得两个机枪炮塔之后重获新生
that will greatly increase its survivability in battle.
同时能大大提高它在战斗中的生存能力
We've also made several exciting additions to the array of ground vehicles available.
我们也对地面载具的科技树做了不少亦可赛艇的更新
The Brummbär self-propelled howitzer will join the ranks of German armored vehicles.
灰熊式自行榴弹炮将加入德国坦克科技树
The short, but destructive 150 millimeter cannon will lob shells weighing 38 kilograms each.
短但是极具威力的150mm坦克炮能把38kg的炮弹发射出去
Few can survive such a shot.
没什么坦克能承受这样的一击
Each hit will either immediately send the opponent back to the hangar
每一发都能迅速地将对手送回车库
or deal such great damage that they won't recover from it.
或者让对手承受不可挽回的巨大损伤
Aim well and you'll be the star of any battle!
好好瞄准 你肯定能成为任何战斗的能手
Next, we have two important additions to ground battles.
接下来 在陆战载具中我们有两项重要的更新
Two new top-tier medium tanks in the US and USSR lines.
美国和苏联科技树中的两辆顶级中坦
The M60A1, the successor to the excellent M60,
M60A1 作为优秀的M60的继任者
is superior to its predecessor in all its characteristics.
无论从哪个方面看都超过了它的前辈
Incredibly thick armor on the front of the turret, an excellent rapid-firing cannon and good mobility.
炮塔正面厚得难以置信的装甲 装填速度快且性能优异的火炮以及不错的机动性
This set of qualities makes the M60A1 the best medium tank in the USA's tech tree.
这些特性将让M60A1成为美国科技树中最强的中坦
Burst into the thick of your enemies, flank them, mercilessly fire from the sides and rear.
冲入敌人的重重包围 包抄他们的侧面 毫不留情地从侧后方开火
Now you have no enemies you can't defeat!
现在没什么敌人是你无法击败的
Soviet tankers are getting the newest medium tank, the T-62,
苏联坦克玩家将获得最新的中坦T-62
the direct successor to the threatening T-54s.
作为极具威胁性的T-54系列的继任者
The main advantage of this tank is its 115 mm cannon,
这辆坦克的最大优点在于它那115mm口径的火炮
designed specifically to combat the newest American tanks.
就是设计出来和美国最新的坦克进行战斗
It's long reload time is more than compensated for
较长的装填时间是用来为
by its excellent armor penetration even with stock shells.
它优秀的穿甲能力（即使使用的是默认弹）作出的牺牲
T-62 is a tank created specially to destroy enemy armor
T-62是专门用来摧毁敌方装甲而生的
It's fast, maneuverable, has excellent protection and a truly deadly cannon.
它具有不错的机动性及优秀的装甲和致命的火炮
Pain and suffering for enemies and pure joy for the owner
对敌人而言是痛苦和折磨而对使用者而言是纯粹的乐趣
– be sure to try out this beauty in battle!
一定要在战斗中尝试一下
Another new vehicle for the US ground forces - the Canadian RAM 2 tank,
另外一个美国陆战载具中的新力量 加拿大公羊巡洋坦克Mk.II
which courageous Canadian tankers trained with before taking part in the heavy battles in Europe.
勇敢的加拿大装甲兵们在参与欧洲的战斗前曾使用它来训练
New arrival to the British line - the legendary two-turret Grant Mk.I ,
英国科技树的更新 传奇般的双炮塔格兰特Mk.I
which will become the first reward for participants in the “Operation Summer” special event.
将会成为“Operation Summer”特殊行动的参与者的第一份奖品
Both tanks are perfectly balanced in terms of armor, speed and armament
这两辆坦克都在装甲 机动性和武器上取得了完美的平衡
and are perfectly suited to any challenge on the battlefield
能够应对战场上遇到的任何挑战
from daring rushes to the stalwart defense of strategic positions.
包括横冲直撞和盯梢黑枪
Try them out in battle, you're sure to like them!
在战斗中试试 你肯定会喜欢上它们的
Another special event tank for those who decide to accomplish all the summer event tasks
对于那些决定要完成所有夏日活动任务的人
will be the experimental Soviet KV-220 tank.
将会得到实验性的苏联坦克KV-220
This vehicle is based on the KV-1 heavy tank and surpasses its predecessor in all respects.
这个载具基于KV-1改造而成但在所有方面都超越了它的前辈
A powerful and accurate 85 mm cannon,
一个强大且足够精确的85mm火炮
armor of up to 100 mm in thickness and a new engine.
厚大100mm的装甲和一台全新的引擎
This tank is a true terminator at its rank.
这辆坦克在同分房内是真正的终结者
A valuable prize for the most tenacious tankers in War Thunder.
作为战争雷霆中坚持不懈的坦克玩家的珍贵奖品
We're also adding the ability to replaced downed new crew members in battle.
我们同时增加了能让昏迷成员在战斗中替换的机制
Thanks to feedback and suggestions from players,
得益于玩家的反馈和建议
we've developed a new game mechanic which will be an optimal solution
我们建立了一种新的游戏机制
to increasing the survivability of tanks on the battlefield.
作为增强陆战载具的生存能力的最佳解决方案
You'll be able to prepare a reserve of an extra crew member before battle,
在战斗前 你能准备一个额外的预备成员
to replace a knocked-out tanker when necessary.
这样的话 在必要时就能用来替换昏迷的成员
In Realistic and Simulator battles, you'll only be able to replace an out-of-action crew member
在历史和全真模式里 你只能在属于自己队伍的战区
at strategic points that belong to your team
替换昏迷的成员
and only on the condition that a minimum of two tankers in your crew are still in action.
并且只能在坦克成员组尚余两名成员的情况下进行
In Arcade battles, it's all simpler – the reserve will arrive automatically at any point on the map
在街机模式中 这就简单多了 在地图的任何位置上 预备成员都会自动填补
as soon as only one tanker is left in your crew.
只要你坦克内只剩一名成员的时候
You can also summon the reserve by pressing a button if a particularly important crew has been injured.
如果有特别重要的成员受伤的时候 你也能通过按键召唤这位预备成员
The reserve tanker is researched as a modification for all War Thunder ground vehicles.
预备成员将成为战争雷霆中所有陆战载具的研发改装件
Excellent news for War Thunder squadrons.
以下是对战争雷霆联队而言极好的新闻
Squadron battles are moving to a full-fledged seasonal system.
联队战斗将成为一套成熟的季赛系统
Each season will last 2 months, with a total of 6 seasons per year.
每季持续两个月 也即每年有六季比赛
Player ratings are reset at the beginning of each season,
玩家的分数将在每季比赛开始的时候清零
so in each season squadrons will have to prove their worth
所以每季比赛玩家都得为他们自己而战
and assert their rights for rewards over again.
并且为他们的报酬再次战斗
And there are going to be more rewards now!
而且从现在开始将会有更多的奖赏
First of all, we've increased the number of prize-winning places with a reward in Golden Eagles from 3 to 20.
首先 我们会增加能拿到金鹰的排名 从第三到第二十的排名都可以拿到
Apart from Golden Eagles, squadrons will now be able to get unique decorative clan tags,
除了金鹰 联队队员也能得到特别的联队装饰品
special decals and trophy marks in tanker profiles
特殊的贴花和纪念品
with the name of the season and position of the squadron in the ranking battles.
带着季赛中的名字和联队在排位赛中的排名
The overall number of prize-winning places is now 100,
前一百名都能获得奖品
and your squadron could be the best of the best!
你的联队也许能创造辉煌
Commanders, lead your troops to victory!
指挥官们 带领你的军队创造胜利吧
A full list of changes coming in War Thunder 1.61 Road To Glory
战争雷霆1.61版本：光荣之路的完整更新报告
can be found on our official site and in the video description.
将能在我们官网和简介处的链接那里找到
Don't forget to subscribe to the official War Thunder channel on Youtube,
别忘了订阅Youtube上的官方频道
join our group on Facebook and follows us on Twitter.
加入我们在Facebook上的小组 并关注我们的Twitter
See you on the battlefield!
战场上再见